// ==UserScript==
// @name                WME Validator Maryland Localization
// @version             0.1.12
// @author              subs5 and xanderb
// @description         This script localizes WME Validator for United States. You also need main package (WME Validator) installed.
// @include             /^https:\/\/(www|beta)\.waze\.com\/(?!user\/)(.{2,6}\/)?editor\/.*$/
// @grant               none
// @run-at              document-start
// @namespace           https://greasyfork.org/en/users/7755-subs5
// ==/UserScript==
//
/*
  Please translate all the lines marked with ""
  Please DO NOT change ".en" properties. To override english text use "titleEN",
  "problemEN" and "solutionEN" properties (see an example below).

  See Settings->About->Available checks for complete list of checks and their params.

  Examples:

  Enable #170 "Lowercase street name" but allow lowercase "exit" and "to":
    "170.enabled": true,
    "170.params": {
        "regexp": "/^((exit|to) )?[a-z]/",
    "},

  Enable #130 "Custom check" to find a dot in street names, but allow dots at Ramps:
    "130.enabled": true,
    "130.params": {
        "titleEN": "Street name with a dot",
        "problemEN": "There is a dot in the street name (excluding Ramps)",
        "solutionEN": "Expand the abbreviation or remove the dot",
        "template": "${type}:${street}",
        "regexp": "D/^[^4][0-9]?:.*\\./",
    },
    *Note: use D at the beginning of RegExp to enable debugging on JS console.
    *Note: do not forget to escape backslashes in strings, i.e. use "\\" instead of "\".
*/

window.WME_Validator_United_States = {
  ".country": "United States",
  ".codeISO": "US",
  ".author": "subs5 and XanderB",
  ".updated": "2017-04-06",
  ".link": "https://greasyfork.org/en/scripts/14467-wme-validator-maryland-localization",
  ".lng": "EN-US",
  "city.consider.en": "consider this city name:",
  "city.consider": "consider this city name:",
  "city.1.en": "city name is too short",
  "city.1": "city name is too short",
  "city.2.en": "expand the abbreviation",
  "city.2": "expand the abbreviation",
  "city.3.en": "complete short name",
  "city.3": "complete short name",
  "city.4.en": "complete city name",
  "city.4": "complete city name",
  "city.5.en": "correct letter case",
  "city.5": "correct letter case",
  "city.6.en": "check word order",
  "city.6": "check word order",
  "city.7.en": "check abbreviations",
  "city.7": "check abbreviations",
  "city.8a.en": "add county name",
  "city.8a": "add county name",
  "city.8r.en": "remove county name",
  "city.8r": "remove county name",
  "city.9.en": "check county name",
  "city.9": "check county name",
  "city.10a.en": "add a word",
  "city.10a": "add a word",
  "city.10r.en": "remove a word",
  "city.10r": "remove a word",
  "city.11.en": "add county code",
  "city.11": "add county code",
  "city.12.en": "identical names, but different city IDs",
  "city.12": "identical names, but different city IDs",
  "city.13a.en": "add a space",
  "city.13a": "add a space",
  "city.13r.en": "remove a space",
  "city.13r": "remove a space",
  "city.14.en": "check the number",
  "city.14": "check the number",
  "props.skipped.title.en": "The segment is not checked",
  "props.skipped.title": "The segment is not checked",
  "props.skipped.problem.en": "The segment is modified after 2014-05-01 AND locked for you, so Validator did not check it",
  "props.skipped.problem": "The segment is modified after 2014-05-01 AND locked for you, so Validator did not check it",
  "err.regexp.en": "Error parsing option for check #${n}:",
  "err.regexp": "Error parsing option for check #${n}:",
  "props.disabled.en": "WME Validator is disabled",
  "props.disabled": "WME Validator is disabled",
  "props.limit.title.en": "Too many issues reported",
  "props.limit.title": "Too many issues reported",
  "props.limit.problem.en": "There are too many issues reported, so some of them might not be shown",
  "props.limit.problem": "There are too many issues reported, so some of them might not be shown",
  "props.limit.solution.en": "Deselect the segment and stop scanning process. Then click red '✘' (Clear report) button",
  "props.limit.solution": "Deselect the segment and stop scanning process. Then click red '✘' (Clear report) button",
  "props.reports.en": "reports",
  "props.reports": "reports",
  "props.noneditable.en": "You cannot edit this segment",
  "props.noneditable": "You cannot edit this segment",
  "report.save.en": "Save this report",
  "report.save": "Save this report",
  "report.list.andUp.en": "and up",
  "report.list.andUp": "and up",
  "report.list.severity.en": "Severity:",
  "report.list.severity": "Severity:",
  "report.list.reportOnly.en": "only in report",
  "report.list.reportOnly": "only in report",
  "report.list.forEditors.en": "For editors level:",
  "report.list.forEditors": "For editors level:",
  "report.list.forCountries.en": "For countries:",
  "report.list.forCountries": "For countries:",
  "report.list.forStates.en": "For states:",
  "report.list.forStates": "For states:",
  "report.list.forCities.en": "For cities:",
  "report.list.forCities": "For cities:",
  "report.list.params.en": "Params to configure in localization pack:",
  "report.list.params": "Params to configure in localization pack:",
  "report.list.params.set.en": "Current configuration for ${country}:",
  "report.list.params.set": "Current configuration for ${country}:",
  "report.list.enabled.en": "${n} checks are enabled for",
  "report.list.enabled": "${n} checks are enabled for",
  "report.list.disabled.en": "${n} checks are disabled for",
  "report.list.disabled": "${n} checks are disabled for",
  "report.list.total.en": "There are ${n} checks available",
  "report.list.total": "There are ${n} checks available",
  "report.list.title.en": "Complete List of Checks for",
  "report.list.title": "Complete List of Checks for",
  "report.list.see.en": "See",
  "report.list.see": "See",
  "report.list.checks.en": "Settings->About->Available checks",
  "report.list.checks": "Settings->About->Available checks",
  "report.list.fallback.en": "Localization Fallback Rules:",
  "report.list.fallback": "Localization Fallback Rules:",
  "report.and.en": "and",
  "report.and": "and",
  "report.segments.en": "Total number of segments checked:",
  "report.segments": "Total number of segments checked:",
  "report.customs.en": "Custom checks matched (green/blue):",
  "report.customs": "Custom checks matched (green/blue):",
  "report.reported.en": "Reported",
  "report.reported": "Reported",
  "report.errors.en": "errors",
  "report.errors": "errors",
  "report.warnings.en": "warnings",
  "report.warnings": "warnings",
  "report.notes.en": "notes",
  "report.notes": "notes",
  "report.link.wiki.en": "wiki",
  "report.link.wiki": "wiki",
  "report.link.forum.en": "forum",
  "report.link.forum": "forum",
  "report.link.other.en": "link",
  "report.link.other": "link",
  "report.contents.en": "Contents:",
  "report.contents": "Contents:",
  "report.summary.en": "Summary",
  "report.summary": "Summary",
  "report.title.en": "WME Validator Report",
  "report.title": "WME Validator Report",
  "report.share.en": "to Share",
  "report.share": "to Share",
  "report.generated.by.en": "generated by",
  "report.generated.by": "generated by",
  "report.generated.on.en": "on",
  "report.generated.on": "on",
  "report.source.en": "Report source:",
  "report.source": "Report source:",
  "report.filter.duplicate.en": "duplicate segments",
  "report.filter.duplicate": "duplicate segments",
  "report.filter.streets.en": "Streets and Service Roads",
  "report.filter.streets": "Streets and Service Roads",
  "report.filter.other.en": "Other drivable and Non-drivable",
  "report.filter.other": "Other drivable and Non-drivable",
  "report.filter.noneditable.en": "non-editable segments",
  "report.filter.noneditable": "non-editable segments",
  "report.filter.notes.en": "notes",
  "report.filter.notes": "notes",
  "report.filter.title.en": "Filter:",
  "report.filter.title": "Filter:",
  "report.filter.excluded.en": "are excluded from this report.",
  "report.filter.excluded": "are excluded from this report.",
  "report.search.updated.by.en": "updated by",
  "report.search.updated.by": "updated by",
  "report.search.updated.since.en": "updated since",
  "report.search.updated.since": "updated since",
  "report.search.city.en": "from",
  "report.search.city": "from",
  "report.search.reported.en": "reported as",
  "report.search.reported": "reported as",
  "report.search.title.en": "Search:",
  "report.search.title": "Search:",
  "report.search.only.en": "only segments",
  "report.search.only": "only segments",
  "report.search.included.en": "are included into the report.",
  "report.search.included": "are included into the report.",
  "report.beta.warning.en": "WME Beta Warning!",
  "report.beta.warning": "WME Beta Warning!",
  "report.beta.text.en": "This report is generated in beta WME with beta permalinks.",
  "report.beta.text": "This report is generated in beta WME with beta permalinks.",
  "report.beta.share.en": "Please do not share those permalinks!",
  "report.beta.share": "Please do not share those permalinks!",
  "report.size.warning.en": "<b>Warning!</b><br>The report is ${n} characters long so <b>it will not fit</b> into a single forum or private message.\n<br>Please add <b>more filters</b> to reduce the size of the report.",
  "report.size.warning": "<b>Warning!</b><br>The report is ${n} characters long so <b>it will not fit</b> into a single forum or private message.\n<br>Please add <b>more filters</b> to reduce the size of the report.",
  "report.note.limit.en": "* Note: there were too many issues reported, so some of them are not counted in the summary.",
  "report.note.limit": "* Note: there were too many issues reported, so some of them are not counted in the summary.",
  "report.forum.en": "To motivate further development please leave your comment on the",
  "report.forum": "To motivate further development please leave your comment on the",
  "report.forum.link.en": "Waze forum thread.",
  "report.forum.link": "Waze forum thread.",
  "report.thanks.en": "Thank you for using WME Validator!",
  "report.thanks": "Thank you for using WME Validator!",
  "msg.limit.segments.en": "There are too many segments.\n\nClick 'Show report' to review the report, then\n",
  "msg.limit.segments": "There are too many segments.\n\nClick 'Show report' to review the report, then\n",
  "msg.limit.segments.continue.en": "click '▶' (Play) to continue.",
  "msg.limit.segments.continue": "click '▶' (Play) to continue.",
  "msg.limit.segments.clear.en": "click '✘' (Clear) to clear the report.",
  "msg.limit.segments.clear": "click '✘' (Clear) to clear the report.",
  "msg.pan.text.en": "Pan around to validate the map",
  "msg.pan.text": "Pan around to validate the map",
  "msg.zoomout.text.en": "Zoom out to start WME Validator",
  "msg.zoomout.text": "Zoom out to start WME Validator",
  "msg.click.text.en": "Click '▶' (Play) to validate visible map area",
  "msg.click.text": "Click '▶' (Play) to validate visible map area",
  "msg.autopaused.en": "autopaused",
  "msg.autopaused": "autopaused",
  "msg.autopaused.text.en": "Auto paused! Click '▶' (Play) to continue.",
  "msg.autopaused.text": "Auto paused! Click '▶' (Play) to continue.",
  "msg.autopaused.tip.en": "WME Validator automatically paused on map drag or window size change",
  "msg.autopaused.tip": "WME Validator automatically paused on map drag or window size change",
  "msg.finished.text.en": "Click <b>'Show report'</b> to review map issues",
  "msg.finished.text": "Click <b>'Show report'</b> to review map issues",
  "msg.finished.tip.en": "Click '✉' (Share) button to post report on a\nforum or in a private message",
  "msg.finished.tip": "Click '✉' (Share) button to post report on a\nforum or in a private message",
  "msg.noissues.text.en": "Finished! No issues found!",
  "msg.noissues.text": "Finished! No issues found!",
  "msg.noissues.tip.en": "Try to uncheck some filter options or start WME Validator over another map area!",
  "msg.noissues.tip": "Try to uncheck some filter options or start WME Validator over another map area!",
  "msg.scanning.text.en": "Scanning! Finishing in ~ ${n} min",
  "msg.scanning.text": "Scanning! Finishing in ~ ${n} min",
  "msg.scanning.text.soon.en": "Scanning! Finishing in a minute!",
  "msg.scanning.text.soon": "Scanning! Finishing in a minute!",
  "msg.scanning.tip.en": "Click 'Pause' button to pause or '■' (Stop) to stop",
  "msg.scanning.tip": "Click 'Pause' button to pause or '■' (Stop) to stop",
  "msg.starting.text.en": "Starting! Layers are off to scan faster!",
  "msg.starting.text": "Starting! Layers are off to scan faster!",
  "msg.starting.tip.en": "Use 'Pause' button to pause or '■' button to stop",
  "msg.starting.tip": "Use 'Pause' button to pause or '■' button to stop",
  "msg.paused.text.en": "On pause! Click '▶' (Play) button to continue.",
  "msg.paused.text": "On pause! Click '▶' (Play) button to continue.",
  "msg.paused.tip.en": "To view the report click 'Show report' button (if available)",
  "msg.paused.tip": "To view the report click 'Show report' button (if available)",
  "msg.continuing.text.en": "Continuing!",
  "msg.continuing.text": "Continuing!",
  "msg.continuing.tip.en": "WME Validator will continue from the location it was paused",
  "msg.continuing.tip": "WME Validator will continue from the location it was paused",
  "msg.settings.text.en": "Click <b>'Back'</b> to return to main view",
  "msg.settings.text": "Click <b>'Back'</b> to return to main view",
  "msg.settings.tip.en": "Click 'Reset defaults' button to reset all settings in one click!",
  "msg.settings.tip": "Click 'Reset defaults' button to reset all settings in one click!",
  "msg.reset.text.en": "All filter options and settings have been reset to their defaults",
  "msg.reset.text": "All filter options and settings have been reset to their defaults",
  "msg.reset.tip.en": "Click 'Back' button to return to main view",
  "msg.reset.tip": "Click 'Back' button to return to main view",
  "msg.textarea.pack.en": "This is a Greasemonkey/Tampermonkey script. You can copy and paste the text below into a <b>new .user.js file</b><br>or <b>paste it directly</b> into the Greasemonkey/Tampermonkey",
  "msg.textarea.pack": "This is a Greasemonkey/Tampermonkey script. You can copy and paste the text below into a <b>new .user.js file</b><br>or <b>paste it directly</b> into the Greasemonkey/Tampermonkey",
  "msg.textarea.en": "Please copy the text below and then paste it into your forum post or private message",
  "msg.textarea": "Please copy the text below and then paste it into your forum post or private message",
  "noaccess.text.en": "<b>Sorry,</b><br>You cannot use WME Validator over here.<br>Please check <a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488'>the forum thread</a><br>for more information.",
  "noaccess.text": "<b>Sorry,</b><br>You cannot use WME Validator over here.<br>Please check <a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488'>the forum thread</a><br>for more information.",
  "noaccess.tip.en": "Please check the forum thread for more information!",
  "noaccess.tip": "Please check the forum thread for more information!",
  "tab.switch.tip.on.en": "Click to switch highlighting on (Alt+V)",
  "tab.switch.tip.on": "Click to switch highlighting on (Alt+V)",
  "tab.switch.tip.off.en": "Click to switch highlighting off (Alt+V)",
  "tab.switch.tip.off": "Click to switch highlighting off (Alt+V)",
  "tab.filter.text.en": "filter",
  "tab.filter.text": "filter",
  "tab.filter.tip.en": "Options to filter the report and highlighted segments",
  "tab.filter.tip": "Options to filter the report and highlighted segments",
  "tab.search.text.en": "search",
  "tab.search.text": "search",
  "tab.search.tip.en": "Advanced filter options to include only specific segments",
  "tab.search.tip": "Advanced filter options to include only specific segments",
  "tab.help.text.en": "help",
  "tab.help.text": "help",
  "tab.help.tip.en": "Need help?",
  "tab.help.tip": "Need help?",
  "filter.noneditables.text.en": "Exclude <b>non-editable</b> segments",
  "filter.noneditables.text": "Exclude <b>non-editable</b> segments",
  "filter.noneditables.tip.en": "Do not report locked segments or\nsegments outside of your editable areas",
  "filter.noneditables.tip": "Do not report locked segments or\nsegments outside of your editable areas",
  "filter.duplicates.text.en": "Exclude <b>duplicate</b> segments",
  "filter.duplicates.text": "Exclude <b>duplicate</b> segments",
  "filter.duplicates.tip.en": "Do not show the same segment in different\nparts of report\n* Note: this option DOES NOT affect highlighting",
  "filter.duplicates.tip": "Do not show the same segment in different\nparts of report\n* Note: this option DOES NOT affect highlighting",
  "filter.streets.text.en": "Exclude <b>Streets and Service Roads</b>",
  "filter.streets.text": "Exclude <b>Streets and Service Roads</b>",
  "filter.streets.tip.en": "Do not report Streets and Service Roads",
  "filter.streets.tip": "Do not report Streets and Service Roads",
  "filter.other.text.en": "Exclude <b>Other drivable and Non-drivable</b>",
  "filter.other.text": "Exclude <b>Other drivable and Non-drivable</b>",
  "filter.other.tip.en": "Do not report Dirt, Parking Lot, Private Roads\nand non-drivable segments",
  "filter.other.tip": "Do not report Dirt, Parking Lot, Private Roads\nand non-drivable segments",
  "filter.notes.text.en": "Exclude <b>notes</b>",
  "filter.notes.text": "Exclude <b>notes</b>",
  "filter.notes.tip.en": "Report only warnings and errors",
  "filter.notes.tip": "Report only warnings and errors",
  "search.youredits.text.en": "Include <b>only your edits</b>",
  "search.youredits.text": "Include <b>only your edits</b>",
  "search.youredits.tip.en": "Include only segments edited by you",
  "search.youredits.tip": "Include only segments edited by you",
  "search.updatedby.text.en": "<b>Updated by*:</b>",
  "search.updatedby.text": "<b>Updated by*:</b>",
  "search.updatedby.tip.en": "Include only segments updated by the specified editor\n* Note: this option is available for country managers only\nThis field supports:\n - lists: me, otherEditor\n - wildcards: world*\n - negation: !me, *\n* Note: you may use 'me' to match yourself",
  "search.updatedby.tip": "Include only segments updated by the specified editor\n* Note: this option is available for country managers only\nThis field supports:\n - lists: me, otherEditor\n - wildcards: world*\n - negation: !me, *\n* Note: you may use 'me' to match yourself",
  "search.updatedby.example.en": "Example: me",
  "search.updatedby.example": "Example: me",
  "search.updatedsince.text.en": "<b>Updated since:</b>",
  "search.updatedsince.text": "<b>Updated since:</b>",
  "search.updatedsince.tip.en": "Include only segments edited since the date specified\nFirefox date format: YYYY-MM-DD",
  "search.updatedsince.tip": "Include only segments edited since the date specified\nFirefox date format: YYYY-MM-DD",
  "search.updatedsince.example.en": "YYYY-MM-DD",
  "search.updatedsince.example": "YYYY-MM-DD",
  "search.city.text.en": "<b>City name:</b>",
  "search.city.text": "<b>City name:</b>",
  "search.city.tip.en": "Include only segments with specified city name\nThis field supports:\n - lists: Paris, Meudon\n - wildcards: Greater * Area\n - negation: !Paris, *",
  "search.city.tip": "Include only segments with specified city name\nThis field supports:\n - lists: Paris, Meudon\n - wildcards: Greater * Area\n - negation: !Paris, *",
  "search.city.example.en": "Example: !Paris, *",
  "search.city.example": "Example: !Paris, *",
  "search.checks.text.en": "<b>Reported as:</b>",
  "search.checks.text": "<b>Reported as:</b>",
  "search.checks.tip.en": "Include only segments reported as specified\nThis field matches:\n - severities: errors\n - check names: New road\n - check IDs: 200\nThis field supports:\n - lists: 36, 37\n - wildcards: *roundabout*\n - negation: !unconfirmed*, *",
  "search.checks.tip": "Include only segments reported as specified\nThis field matches:\n - severities: errors\n - check names: New road\n - check IDs: 200\nThis field supports:\n - lists: 36, 37\n - wildcards: *roundabout*\n - negation: !unconfirmed*, *",
  "search.checks.example.en": "Example: reverse*",
  "search.checks.example": "Example: reverse*",
  "help.text.en": "<b>Help Topics:</b><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=666476#p666476\">F.A.Q.</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488\">Ask your question on the forum</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=661300#p661185\">How to adjust Validator for your country</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=663286#p663286\">About the \"Might be Incorrect City Name\"</a>",
  "help.text": "<b>Help Topics:</b><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=666476#p666476\">F.A.Q.</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488\">Ask your question on the forum</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=661300#p661185\">How to adjust Validator for your country</a><br><a target=\"_blank\" href=\"https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=663286#p663286\">About the \"Might be Incorrect City Name\"</a>",
  "help.tip.en": "Open in a new browser tab",
  "help.tip": "Open in a new browser tab",
  "button.scan.tip.en": "Start scanning current map area\n* Note: this might take few minutes",
  "button.scan.tip": "Start scanning current map area\n* Note: this might take few minutes",
  "button.scan.tip.NA.en": "Zoom out to start scanning current map area",
  "button.scan.tip.NA": "Zoom out to start scanning current map area",
  "button.pause.tip.en": "Pause scanning",
  "button.pause.tip": "Pause scanning",
  "button.continue.tip.en": "Continue scanning the map area",
  "button.continue.tip": "Continue scanning the map area",
  "button.stop.tip.en": "Stop scanning and return to the start position",
  "button.stop.tip": "Stop scanning and return to the start position",
  "button.clear.tip.en": "Clear report and segment cache",
  "button.clear.tip": "Clear report and segment cache",
  "button.clear.tip.red.en": "There are too many reported segments:\n 1. Click 'Show report' to generate the report.\n 2. Click this button to clear the report and start over.",
  "button.clear.tip.red": "There are too many reported segments:\n 1. Click 'Show report' to generate the report.\n 2. Click this button to clear the report and start over.",
  "button.report.text.en": "Show report",
  "button.report.text": "Show report",
  "button.report.tip.en": "Apply the filter and generate HTML report in a new tab",
  "button.report.tip": "Apply the filter and generate HTML report in a new tab",
  "button.BBreport.tip.en": "Share the report on Waze forum or in a private message",
  "button.BBreport.tip": "Share the report on Waze forum or in a private message",
  "button.settings.tip.en": "Configure settings",
  "button.settings.tip": "Configure settings",
  "tab.custom.text.en": "custom",
  "tab.custom.text": "custom",
  "tab.custom.tip.en": "User-defined custom checks settings",
  "tab.custom.tip": "User-defined custom checks settings",
  "tab.settings.text.en": "Settings",
  "tab.settings.text": "Settings",
  "tab.scanner.text.en": "scanner",
  "tab.scanner.text": "scanner",
  "tab.scanner.tip.en": "Map scanner settings",
  "tab.scanner.tip": "Map scanner settings",
  "tab.about.text.en": "about</span>",
  "tab.about.text": "about</span>",
  "tab.about.tip.en": "About WME Validator",
  "tab.about.tip": "About WME Validator",
  "scanner.sounds.text.en": "Enable sounds",
  "scanner.sounds.text": "Enable sounds",
  "scanner.sounds.tip.en": "Bleeps and the bloops while scanning",
  "scanner.sounds.tip": "Bleeps and the bloops while scanning",
  "scanner.sounds.NA.en": "Your browser does not support AudioContext",
  "scanner.sounds.NA": "Your browser does not support AudioContext",
  "scanner.highlight.text.en": "Highlight issues on the map",
  "scanner.highlight.text": "Highlight issues on the map",
  "scanner.highlight.tip.en": "Highlight reported issues on the map",
  "scanner.highlight.tip": "Highlight reported issues on the map",
  "scanner.slow.text.en": "Enable \"slow\" checks",
  "scanner.slow.text": "Enable \"slow\" checks",
  "scanner.slow.tip.en": "Enables deep map analysis\n* Note: this option might slow down the scanning process",
  "scanner.slow.tip": "Enables deep map analysis\n* Note: this option might slow down the scanning process",
  "scanner.ext.text.en": "Report external highlights",
  "scanner.ext.text": "Report external highlights",
  "scanner.ext.tip.en": "Report segments highlighted by WME Toolbox or WME Color Highlights",
  "scanner.ext.tip": "Report segments highlighted by WME Toolbox or WME Color Highlights",
  "custom.template.text.en": "<a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=749456#p749456'>Custom template</a>",
  "custom.template.text": "<a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=749456#p749456'>Custom template</a>",
  "custom.template.tip.en": "User-defined custom check expandable template.\n\nYou may use the following expandable variables:\nAddress:\n  ${country}, ${state}, ${city}, ${street},\n  ${altCity[index or delimeter]}, ${altStreet[index or delimeter]}\nSegment properties:\n  ${type}, ${typeRank}, ${toll}, ${direction}, ${elevation}, ${lock},\n  ${length}, ${ID}\nHelpers:\n  ${drivable}, ${roundabout}, ${hasHNs},\n  ${Uturn}, ${deadEnd}, ${softTurns},\n  ${deadEndA}, ${partialA},\n  ${deadEndB}, ${partialB}\nConnectivity:\n  ${segmentsA}, ${inA}, ${outA}, ${UturnA},\n  ${segmentsB}, ${inB}, ${outB}, ${UturnB}",
  "custom.template.tip": "User-defined custom check expandable template.\n\nYou may use the following expandable variables:\nAddress:\n  ${country}, ${state}, ${city}, ${street},\n  ${altCity[index or delimeter]}, ${altStreet[index or delimeter]}\nSegment properties:\n  ${type}, ${typeRank}, ${toll}, ${direction}, ${elevation}, ${lock},\n  ${length}, ${ID}\nHelpers:\n  ${drivable}, ${roundabout}, ${hasHNs},\n  ${Uturn}, ${deadEnd}, ${softTurns},\n  ${deadEndA}, ${partialA},\n  ${deadEndB}, ${partialB}\nConnectivity:\n  ${segmentsA}, ${inA}, ${outA}, ${UturnA},\n  ${segmentsB}, ${inB}, ${outB}, ${UturnB}",
  "custom.template.example.en": "Example: ${street}",
  "custom.template.example": "Example: ${street}",
  "custom.regexp.text.en": "Custom <a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=749456#p749456'>RegExp</a>",
  "custom.regexp.text": "Custom <a target='_blank' href='https://www.waze.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=76488&p=749456#p749456'>RegExp</a>",
  "custom.regexp.tip.en": "User-defined custom check regular expression to match the template.\n\nCase-insensitive match: /regexp/i\nNegation (do not match): !/regexp/\nLog debug information on console: D/regexp/",
  "custom.regexp.tip": "User-defined custom check regular expression to match the template.\n\nCase-insensitive match: /regexp/i\nNegation (do not match): !/regexp/\nLog debug information on console: D/regexp/",
  "custom.regexp.example.en": "Example: !/.+/",
  "custom.regexp.example": "Example: !/.+/",
  "about.tip.en": "Open link in a new tab",
  "about.tip": "Open link in a new tab",
  "button.reset.text.en": "Reset defaults",
  "button.reset.text": "Reset defaults",
  "button.reset.tip.en": "Revert filter options and settings to their defaults",
  "button.reset.tip": "Revert filter options and settings to their defaults",
  "button.list.text.en": "Available checks...",
  "button.list.text": "Available checks...",
  "button.list.tip.en": "Show a list of checks available in WME Validator",
  "button.list.tip": "Show a list of checks available in WME Validator",
  "button.wizard.tip.en": "Create localization package",
  "button.wizard.tip": "Create localization package",
  "button.back.text.en": "Back",
  "button.back.text": "Back",
  "button.back.tip.en": "Close settings and return to main view",
  "button.back.tip": "Close settings and return to main view",
  "1.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Roundabout which may cause issues",
  "1.title": "WME Toolbox: Roundabout which may cause issues",
  "1.problem.en": "Junction IDs of the roundabout segments are not consecutive",
  "1.problem": "Junction IDs of the roundabout segments are not consecutive",
  "1.solution.en": "Redo the roundabout",
  "1.solution": "Redo the roundabout",
  "2.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Simple segment",
  "2.title": "WME Toolbox: Simple segment",
  "2.problem.en": "The segment has unneeded geometry nodes",
  "2.problem": "The segment has unneeded geometry nodes",
  "2.solution.en": "Simplify segment geometry by hovering mouse pointer and pressing \"d\" key",
  "2.solution": "Simplify segment geometry by hovering mouse pointer and pressing \"d\" key",
  "3.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 2 lock",
  "3.title": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 2 lock",
  "3.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "3.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "4.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 3 lock",
  "4.title": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 3 lock",
  "4.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "4.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "5.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 4 lock",
  "5.title": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 4 lock",
  "5.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "5.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "6.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 5 lock",
  "6.title": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 5 lock",
  "6.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "6.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "7.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 6 lock",
  "7.title": "WME Toolbox: Lvl 6 lock",
  "7.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "7.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "8.title.en": "WME Toolbox: House numbers",
  "8.title": "WME Toolbox: House numbers",
  "8.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "8.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "9.title.en": "WME Toolbox: Segment with time restrictions",
  "9.title": "WME Toolbox: Segment with time restrictions",
  "9.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "9.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Toolbox. It is not a problem",
  "13.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Editor lock",
  "13.title": "WME Color Highlights: Editor lock",
  "13.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "13.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "14.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Toll road / One way road",
  "14.title": "WME Color Highlights: Toll road / One way road",
  "14.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "14.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "15.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Recently edited",
  "15.title": "WME Color Highlights: Recently edited",
  "15.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "15.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "16.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Road rank",
  "16.title": "WME Color Highlights: Road rank",
  "16.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "16.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "17.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: No city",
  "17.title": "WME Color Highlights: No city",
  "17.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "17.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "18.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Time restriction / Highlighted road type",
  "18.title": "WME Color Highlights: Time restriction / Highlighted road type",
  "18.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "18.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "19.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: No name",
  "19.title": "WME Color Highlights: No name",
  "19.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "19.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "20.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by city",
  "20.title": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by city",
  "20.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "20.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "21.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by city (alt. city)",
  "21.title": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by city (alt. city)",
  "21.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "21.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "22.title.en": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by editor",
  "22.title": "WME Color Highlights: Filter by editor",
  "22.problem.en": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "22.problem": "The segment is highlighted by WME Color Highlights. It is not a problem",
  "23.title.en": "Unconfirmed road",
  "23.title": "Unconfirmed road",
  "23.problem.en": "Each segment must minimally have the Country and State information",
  "23.problem": "Each segment must minimally have the Country and State information",
  "23.solution.en": "Confirm the road by updating its details",
  "23.solution": "Confirm the road by updating its details",
  "24.title.en": "Might be incorrect city name (only available in the report)",
  "24.title": "Might be incorrect city name (only available in the report)",
  "24.problem.en": "The segment might have incorrect city name",
  "24.problem": "The segment might have incorrect city name",
  "24.solution.en": "Consider suggested city name and use this form to rename the city",
  "24.solution": "Consider suggested city name and use this form to rename the city",
  "25.title.en": "Unknown direction of drivable road",
  "25.title": "Unknown direction of drivable road",
  "25.problem.en": "'Unknown' road direction will not prevent routing on the road",
  "25.problem": "'Unknown' road direction will not prevent routing on the road",
  "25.solution.en": "Set the road direction",
  "25.solution": "Set the road direction",
  "27.enabled": true,
  "27.title.en": "City name on Railroad",
  "27.title": "City name on Railroad",
  "27.problem.en": "City name on the Railroad may cause a city smudge",
  "27.problem": "City name on the Railroad may cause a city smudge",
  "27.solution.en": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the city name and then click 'Apply'",
  "27.solution": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the city name and then click 'Apply'",
  "28.title.en": "Street name on two-way Ramp",
  "28.title": "Street name on two-way Ramp",
  "28.problem.en": "If Ramp is unnamed, the name of a subsequent road will propagate backwards",
  "28.problem": "If Ramp is unnamed, the name of a subsequent road will propagate backwards",
  "28.solution.en": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name and then click 'Apply'",
  "28.solution": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name and then click 'Apply'",
  "29.title.en": "Street name on roundabout",
  "29.title": "Street name on roundabout",
  "29.problem.en": "In Waze, we do not name roundabout segments",
  "29.problem": "In Waze, we do not name roundabout segments",
  "29.solution.en": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name, click 'Apply' and then add 'Junction' landmark to name the roundabout",
  "29.solution": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name, click 'Apply' and then add 'Junction' landmark to name the roundabout",
  "34.title.en": "Empty alternate street",
  "34.title": "Empty alternate street",
  "34.problem.en": "Alternate street name is empty",
  "34.problem": "Alternate street name is empty",
  "34.solution.en": "Remove empty alternate street name",
  "34.solution": "Remove empty alternate street name",
  "35.title.en": "Unterminated drivable road",
  "35.title": "Unterminated drivable road",
  "35.problem.en": "Waze will not route from the unterminated segment",
  "35.problem": "Waze will not route from the unterminated segment",
  "35.solution.en": "Move the segment a bit so the terminating node will be added automatically",
  "35.solution": "Move the segment a bit so the terminating node will be added automatically",
  "38.title.en": "Expired segment restriction (slow)",
  "38.title": "Expired segment restriction (slow)",
  "38.problem.en": "The segment has an expired restriction",
  "38.problem": "The segment has an expired restriction",
  "38.solution.en": "Click 'Edit restrictions' and delete the expired restriction",
  "38.solution": "Click 'Edit restrictions' and delete the expired restriction",
  "39.title.en": "Expired turn restriction (slow)",
  "39.title": "Expired turn restriction (slow)",
  "39.problem.en": "The segment has a turn with an expired restriction",
  "39.problem": "The segment has a turn with an expired restriction",
  "39.solution.en": "Click clock icon next to the yellow arrow and delete the expired restriction",
  "39.solution": "Click clock icon next to the yellow arrow and delete the expired restriction",
  "41.title.en": "Node A: Reverse connectivity of drivable road",
  "41.title": "Node A: Reverse connectivity of drivable road",
  "41.problem.en": "There is a turn which goes against the directionality of the segment at node A",
  "41.problem": "There is a turn which goes against the directionality of the segment at node A",
  "41.solution.en": "Make the segment 'Two-way', restrict all the turns at node A and then make the segment 'One way (A→B)' again",
  "41.solution": "Make the segment 'Two-way', restrict all the turns at node A and then make the segment 'One way (A→B)' again",
  "42.title.en": "Node B: Reverse connectivity of drivable road",
  "42.title": "Node B: Reverse connectivity of drivable road",
  "42.problem.en": "There is a turn which goes against the directionality of the segment at node B",
  "42.problem": "There is a turn which goes against the directionality of the segment at node B",
  "42.solution.en": "Make the segment 'Two-way', restrict all the turns at node B and then make the segment 'One way (B→A)' again",
  "42.solution": "Make the segment 'Two-way', restrict all the turns at node B and then make the segment 'One way (B→A)' again",
  "43.title.en": "Self connectivity",
  "43.title": "Self connectivity",
  "43.problem.en": "The segment is connected back to itself",
  "43.problem": "The segment is connected back to itself",
  "43.solution.en": "Split the segment into THREE pieces",
  "43.solution": "Split the segment into THREE pieces",
  "46.title.en": "Node A: No inward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "46.title": "Node A: No inward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "46.problem.en": "The drivable non-private segment has no single inward turn enabled at node A",
  "46.problem": "The drivable non-private segment has no single inward turn enabled at node A",
  "46.solution.en": "Select an adjacent segment and enable at least one turn to the segment at node A",
  "46.solution": "Select an adjacent segment and enable at least one turn to the segment at node A",
  "47.title.en": "Node B: No inward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "47.title": "Node B: No inward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "47.problem.en": "The drivable non-private segment has no single inward turn enabled at node B",
  "47.problem": "The drivable non-private segment has no single inward turn enabled at node B",
  "47.solution.en": "Select an adjacent segment and enable at least one turn to the segment at node B",
  "47.solution": "Select an adjacent segment and enable at least one turn to the segment at node B",
  "48.title.en": "Two-way drivable roundabout segment",
  "48.title": "Two-way drivable roundabout segment",
  "48.problem.en": "The drivable roundabout segment is bidirectional",
  "48.problem": "The drivable roundabout segment is bidirectional",
  "48.solution.en": "Redo the roundabout",
  "48.solution": "Redo the roundabout",
  "78.title.en": "Same endpoints drivable segments (slow)",
  "78.title": "Same endpoints drivable segments (slow)",
  "78.problem.en": "Two drivable segments share the same two endpoints",
  "78.problem": "Two drivable segments share the same two endpoints",
  "78.solution.en": "Split the segment. You might also remove one of the segments if they are identical",
  "78.solution": "Split the segment. You might also remove one of the segments if they are identical",
  "87.title.en": "Node A: Multiple outgoing segments at roundabout",
  "87.title": "Node A: Multiple outgoing segments at roundabout",
  "87.problem.en": "The drivable roundabout node A has more than one outgoing segment connected",
  "87.problem": "The drivable roundabout node A has more than one outgoing segment connected",
  "87.solution.en": "Redo the roundabout",
  "87.solution": "Redo the roundabout",
  "90.enabled": true,
  "90.title.en": "Two-way Freeway segment",
  "90.title": "Two-way Freeway segment",
  "90.problem.en": "Most of the Freeways are split into two one-way roads, so this two-way segment might be a mistake",
  "90.problem": "Most of the Freeways are split into two one-way roads, so this two-way segment might be a mistake",
  "90.solution.en": "Check Freeway direction",
  "90.solution": "Check Freeway direction",
  "99.title.en": "U-turn at roundabout entrance (slow)",
  "99.title": "U-turn at roundabout entrance (slow)",
  "99.problem.en": "The roundabout entrance segment has a U-turn enabled",
  "99.problem": "The roundabout entrance segment has a U-turn enabled",
  "99.solution.en": "Disable U-turn",
  "99.solution": "Disable U-turn",
  "101.title.en": "Closed road (only available in the report)",
  "101.title": "Closed road (only available in the report)",
  "101.problem.en": "The segment is marked as closed",
  "101.problem": "The segment is marked as closed",
  "101.solution.en": "If the construction is done, restore the segment connectivity and remove the suffix",
  "101.solution": "If the construction is done, restore the segment connectivity and remove the suffix",
  "102.title.en": "Node A: No outward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "102.title": "Node A: No outward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "102.problem.en": "The drivable segment has no single outward turn enabled at node A",
  "102.problem": "The drivable segment has no single outward turn enabled at node A",
  "102.solution.en": "Enable at least one outward turn from the segment at node A",
  "102.solution": "Enable at least one outward turn from the segment at node A",
  "103.title.en": "Node B: No outward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "103.title": "Node B: No outward connectivity of drivable road (slow)",
  "103.problem.en": "The drivable segment has no single outward turn enabled at node B",
  "103.problem": "The drivable segment has no single outward turn enabled at node B",
  "103.solution.en": "Enable at least one outward turn from the segment at node B",
  "103.solution": "Enable at least one outward turn from the segment at node B",
  "104.title.en": "Railroad used for comments",
  "104.title": "Railroad used for comments",
  "104.problem.en": "The Railroad segment is probably used as a map comment",
  "104.problem": "The Railroad segment is probably used as a map comment",
  "104.solution.en": "Remove the comment as Railroads will be added to the client display",
  "104.solution": "Remove the comment as Railroads will be added to the client display",
  "106.enabled": true,
  "106.title.en": "No state name selected",
  "106.title": "No state name selected",
  "106.problem.en": "The segment has no state name selected",
  "106.problem": "The segment has no state name selected",
  "106.solution.en": "Select a state for the segment and apply the changes",
  "106.solution": "Select a state for the segment and apply the changes",
  "107.title.en": "Node A: No connection (slow)",
  "107.title": "Node A: No connection (slow)",
  "107.problem.en": "The node A of the drivable segment is within 5m from another drivable segment but not connected by a junction",
  "107.problem": "The node A of the drivable segment is within 5m from another drivable segment but not connected by a junction",
  "107.solution.en": "Drag the node A to the nearby segment so that it touches or move it a bit further away",
  "107.solution": "Drag the node A to the nearby segment so that it touches or move it a bit further away",
  "108.title.en": "Node B: No connection (slow)",
  "108.title": "Node B: No connection (slow)",
  "108.problem.en": "The node B of the drivable segment is within 5m from another drivable segment but not connected by a junction",
  "108.problem": "The node B of the drivable segment is within 5m from another drivable segment but not connected by a junction",
  "108.solution.en": "Drag the node B to the nearby segment so that it touches or move it a bit further away",
  "108.solution": "Drag the node B to the nearby segment so that it touches or move it a bit further away",
  "109.title.en": "Too short segment",
  "109.title": "Too short segment",
  "109.problem.en": "The drivable non-terminal segment is less than ${n}m long so it is hard to see it on the map and it can cause routing problems",
  "109.problem": "The drivable non-terminal segment is less than ${n}m long so it is hard to see it on the map and it can cause routing problems",
  "109.solution.en": "Increase the length, or remove the segment, or join it with one of the adjacent segments",
  "109.solution": "Increase the length, or remove the segment, or join it with one of the adjacent segments",
  "112.enabled": false,
  "112.title.en": "Too long Ramp name",
  "112.title": "Too long Ramp name",
  "112.problem.en": "The Ramp name is more than ${n} letters long",
  "112.problem": "The Ramp name is more than ${n} letters long",
  "112.solution.en": "Shorten the Ramp name",
  "112.solution": "Shorten the Ramp name",
  "114.title.en": "Node A: Non-drivable connected to drivable (slow)",
  "114.title": "Node A: Non-drivable connected to drivable (slow)",
  "114.problem.en": "The non-drivable segment makes a junction with a drivable at node A",
  "114.problem": "The non-drivable segment makes a junction with a drivable at node A",
  "114.solution.en": "Disconnect node A from all of the drivable segments",
  "114.solution": "Disconnect node A from all of the drivable segments",
  "115.title.en": "Node B: Non-drivable connected to drivable (slow)",
  "115.title": "Node B: Non-drivable connected to drivable (slow)",
  "115.problem.en": "The non-drivable segment makes a junction with a drivable at node B",
  "115.problem": "The non-drivable segment makes a junction with a drivable at node B",
  "115.solution.en": "Disconnect node B from all of the drivable segments",
  "115.solution": "Disconnect node B from all of the drivable segments",
  "116.title.en": "Out of range elevation",
  "116.title": "Out of range elevation",
  "116.problem.en": "The segment elevation is out of range",
  "116.problem": "The segment elevation is out of range",
  "116.solution.en": "Correct the elevation",
  "116.solution": "Correct the elevation",
  "117.title.en": "Obsolete CONST ZN marker",
  "117.title": "Obsolete CONST ZN marker",
  "117.problem.en": "The segment is marked with obsolete CONST ZN suffix",
  "117.problem": "The segment is marked with obsolete CONST ZN suffix",
  "117.solution.en": "Change CONST ZN to (closed)",
  "117.solution": "Change CONST ZN to (closed)",
  "118.title.en": "Node A: Overlapping segments (slow)",
  "118.title": "Node A: Overlapping segments (slow)",
  "118.problem.en": "The segment is overlapping with the adjacent segment at node A",
  "118.problem": "The segment is overlapping with the adjacent segment at node A",
  "118.solution.en": "Spread the segments at 2° or delete unneeded geometry point or delete the duplicate segment at node A",
  "118.solution": "Spread the segments at 2° or delete unneeded geometry point or delete the duplicate segment at node A",
  "119.title.en": "Node B: Overlapping segments (slow)",
  "119.title": "Node B: Overlapping segments (slow)",
  "119.problem.en": "The segment is overlapping with the adjacent segment at node B",
  "119.problem": "The segment is overlapping with the adjacent segment at node B",
  "119.solution.en": "Spread the segments at 2° or delete unneeded geometry point or delete the duplicate segment at node B",
  "119.solution": "Spread the segments at 2° or delete unneeded geometry point or delete the duplicate segment at node B",
  "120.title.en": "Node A: Too sharp turn (slow)",
  "120.title": "Node A: Too sharp turn (slow)",
  "120.problem.en": "The drivable segment has a very acute turn at node A",
  "120.problem": "The drivable segment has a very acute turn at node A",
  "120.solution.en": "Disable the sharp turn at node A or spread the segments at 30°",
  "120.solution": "Disable the sharp turn at node A or spread the segments at 30°",
  "121.title.en": "Node B: Too sharp turn (slow)",
  "121.title": "Node B: Too sharp turn (slow)",
  "121.problem.en": "The drivable segment has a very acute turn at node B",
  "121.problem": "The drivable segment has a very acute turn at node B",
  "121.solution.en": "Disable the sharp turn at node B or spread the segments at 30°",
  "121.solution": "Disable the sharp turn at node B or spread the segments at 30°",
  "128.enabled": true,
  "128.params": {
    "titleEN": "Check Name Suffix",
    "problemEN": "Street suffix does not follow abbreviation rules",
    "solutionEN": "Rename the suffix Such as Road to Rd Please let me know about false positives - subs5",
    "template": "${street}",
    "regexp": "!/(Unknown Name| A(cres?|ly|nnex|ve|r(cade|tery))| B(ay|ch|end|lvd|luf|roadway|ypass|YP|r(a(e|nch|ook))?|ottom|(ike|us)way|ayou)| C(enters|t|lb?|hase|ommons?|o(urse|rs|rner)|ONN|amp|r(es|est|k)?|ir|swy|tr|v|u(rve|toff)|yn)| D(am|ale|ell|onws|r)| E(ast|dgeway|n(d|t)|xit|states?|splanade|x(t|pwy))| F(airway|or(rges?|d|ks?)|wy|alls?|lats?)| G(ardens?|len|rv|r(ee)?n|a(p|te(way)?))| H(arborr|ills?|ollows?|ts|wy|ospital)| I(sle|nlt)| Junctions?| K(eys?|nolls?)| L(ocks?|dg|in[ke]|f|gts?|ndg|[np])|oop| M(all|dw|eadows|nr|anors|t|tns?|ile|o(hr|torway)|ews|sn)| N(eck|orth)| O(aks|ne|rchard|v(al|er(look|pass)))| P(a(ss|th|rade)|ike|romanade|o(intes?|rts?)|l(ns|z)?|k(e|s)?|kwys?|ts?)| R(d|e(ach|st)|ow|i(se|ver)|amp|ailroad|nch|\.R\.|ailway|pds|idge|u(n(way)?|e)|te)| S(ho(als?|res?)|kwy|outh|p(ur|ngs|ring)|u(permarket|bdivision)|t(a|rut)|[qt]s?)| T(er|hwy|lwy|race|pke?|un|urn|r(l|fy)|ra(ck|in))| U(nderpass|pr)| V(iews?|i(llages?|sta)|ly|alleys|iaduct)| W(alk|ays?|ls?|est|oods|ynde?)| X(-ing|rd)| Yard|^$)( [SNEW]{1,2})?$|^([SNEW]{1,2} )?(Old )?(\\d{1,4} [SNEW]|Broadway|MBTA|Railroad|Amtrak|I-|IN-|IA-|KY?-|US-|LA?-|M[DNSO]?-|N[VJYCD]?-|S[CDRH]?-|RI?-|TN-|V[AT]-|W(V|IS)-|C[RH]-|Runway|Place |Parkway|Route |Rue de |Access |Avenue of |Circle of |State |County |The |to |(Left )?E(xit( to:)?|ntry) )/"
  },
  "128.solutionLink": "W:User:Xanderb/Abbreviations",
  "128.title.en": "User-defined custom check (green)",
  "128.title": "Check Name Suffix",
  "128.problem.en": "Some of the segment properties matched against the user-defined regular expression (see Settings→Custom)",
  "128.problem": "Street suffix does not follow abbreviation rules",
  "128.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "128.solution": "Rename the suffix Such as Road to Rd Please let me know about false positives -subs5",
  "129.enabled": true,
  "129.params": {
    "titleEN": "Incorrect Highway Name",
    "problemEN": "Highway names is invalid",
    "solutionEN": "Rename the Street or Alt Street to the current standard",
    "template": "${state}:${street}#${altStreet[#]}",
    "regexp": "/Maryland:.*(Md Hwy |State Hwy |I- |Md-|SR-|SH-|State Rd |MD=|State Rte |^Rte |MD-0|U\.?[Ss]\.? [Hh](WY|wy|ighway))/"
  },
  "129.solutionLink": "W:Maryland#Major_roads",
  "129.title.en": "User-defined custom check (blue)",
  "129.title": "Incorrect Highway Name",
  "129.problem.en": "Some of the segment properties matched against the user-defined regular expression (see Settings→Custom)",
  "129.problem": "Highway names is invalid",
  "129.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "129.solution": "Rename the Street or Alt Street to the current standard",
  "130.enabled": true,
  "130.params": {
    "titleEN": "Potential Incorrect Abbreviation",
    "problemEN": "Name abbreviation may be incorrect. Alternative routes should be labeled ALT and abbreviations ALT, BUS, BYP, CONN, LOOP, SCN, SPUR, or TRUCK should be in ALL CAPS",
    "solutionEN": "Change abbreviation to ALT, BUS, BYP, CONN, LOOP, SCN, SPUR, or TRUCK in ALL CAPS",
    "template": "${street}##${altStreet[0]}##${altStreet[1]}##${altStreet[2]}##${altStreet[3]}##${altStreet[4]}##${altStreet[5]}##${altStreet[6]}##${altStreet[7]}##${altStreet[8]}##${altStreet[9]}",
    "regexp": "/!?[0-9].+(Alt|Business|Bus|Byp|Conn|Loop|Scn|Spur|Truck)\\b/"
  },
  "130.title.en": "Custom check",
  "130.title": "Potential Incorrect Abbreviation",
  "130.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "130.problem": "Name abbreviation may be incorrect. Alternative routes should be labeled ALT and abbreviations ALT, BUS, BYP, CONN, LOOP, SCN, SPUR, or TRUCK should be in ALL CAPS",
  "130.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "130.solution": "Change abbreviation to ALT, BUS, BYP, CONN, LOOP, SCN, SPUR, or TRUCK in ALL CAPS",
  "131.enabled": true,
  "131.params": {
   "title": "Wrong name on US Highway",
    "problem": "All US highways should be named US-###",
    "solution": "Change name to US-###",
    "template": "${street}##${altStreet[0]}##${altStreet[1]}##${altStreet[2]}##${altStreet[3]}##${altStreet[4]}##${altStreet[5]}##${altStreet[6]}##${altStreet[7]}##${altStreet[8]}##${altStreet[9]}",
    "regexp": ".*\\b(?:US Highway |US Hwy Route |US Hwy Rte |US Hwy |US Rte |US- |US )[0-9]{1,3}\\b/i"
  },
  "131.solutionLink": "W:Maryland#Roads",
  "131.title.en": "Custom check",
  "131.title": "Wrong name on US Highway",
  "131.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "131.problem": "All US highways should be named US-###",
  "131.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "131.solution": "Change name to US-###",
  "132.enabled": true,
  "132.params": {
    "titleEN": "Wrong road type (Major)",
    "problemEN": "All US Highways should be at least Major Highway (except BUS, SPUR, LOOP)",
    "solutionEN": "Change the road type to Major Highway",
    "template": "${typeRank}#${street}@#${altStreet[0]}@#${altStreet[1]}@#${altStreet[2]}@#${altStreet[3]}@#${altStreet[4]}@#${altStreet[5]}@#${altStreet[6]}@#${altStreet[7]}@#${altStreet[8]}@#${altStreet[9]}@",
    "regexp": "/^[1-9](?![245]).*#(?:US Hwy |US-)[0-9]+(?: ALT| BYP| CONN| TRUCK| SCN| Scenic| [NSWE])*@/i"
  },
  "132.solutionLink": "W:Road_types/USA#Major_Highway",
  "132.title.en": "Custom check",
  "132.title": "Wrong road type (Major)",
  "132.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "132.problem": "All US Highways should be at least Major Highway (except BUS, SPUR, LOOP)",
  "132.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "132.solution": "Change the road type to Major Highway",
  "133.enabled": true,
  "133.params": {
    "titleEN": "Wrong road type (Minor)",
    "problemEN": "All US BUS, SPUR, LOOP Highways and all State Highways (except BUS, SPUR, LOOP) should be at least Minor Highway type",
    "solutionEN": "Change the road type to Minor Highway",
    "template": "${typeRank}#${street}@#${altStreet[0]}@#${altStreet[1]}@#${altStreet[2]}@#${altStreet[3]}@#${altStreet[4]}@#${altStreet[5]}@#${altStreet[6]}@#${altStreet[7]}@#${altStreet[8]}@#${altStreet[9]}@",
    "regexp": "/^[1-9](?![2-5]).*#(?:(?:State Hwy |SH-|K-|LA-|M-|MA-|MS-|NC-|SC-)[0-9]+(?:| ALT| BYP| CONN| TRUCK| SCN| Scenic| [NSWE])*|(?:US Hwy |US-)[0-9]+(?: BUS| LOOP| SPUR)+(?: [NSWE])?)@/i"
  },
  "133.solutionLink": "W:Road_types/USA#Minor_Highway",
  "133.title.en": "Custom check",
  "133.title": "Wrong road type (Minor)",
  "133.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "133.problem": "All US BUS, SPUR, LOOP Highways and all State Highways (except BUS, SPUR, LOOP) should be at least Minor Highway type",
  "133.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "133.solution": "Change the road type to Minor Highway",
  "134.enabled": true,
  "134.params": {
    "titleEN": "Wrong road type (Primary)",
    "problemEN": "All State BUS, SPUR, LOOP Highways should be at least Primary Street type",
    "solutionEN": "Change the road type to Primary Street",
    "template": "${typeRank}#${street}@#${altStreet[0]}@#${altStreet[1]}@#${altStreet[2]}@#${altStreet[3]}@#${altStreet[4]}@#${altStreet[5]}@#${altStreet[6]}@#${altStreet[7]}@#${altStreet[8]}@#${altStreet[9]}@",
    "regexp": "/^[1-9](?![1-5]).*#(?:State Hwy |SH-|K-|LA-|M-|MA-|MS-|NC-|SC-)[0-9]+(?: BUS| LOOP| SPUR)+(?: [NSWE])?@/i"
  },
  "134.solutionLink": "W:Road_types/USA#Primary_Street",
  "134.title.en": "Custom check",
  "134.title": "Wrong road type (Primary)",
  "134.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "134.problem": "All State BUS, SPUR, LOOP Highways should be at least Primary Street type",
  "134.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "134.solution": "Change the road type to Primary Street",
  "135.enabled": true,
  "135.params": {
    "titleEN": "Not MD State",
    "problemEN": "Incorrect State Name - State name should be Maryland (are you in Maryland?)",
    "solutionEN": "Verify correct state name on segment.",
    "template": "${state}",
    "regexp": "!/^Maryland$/"
  },
  "135.solutionLink": "W:Maryland",
  "135.title.en": "Custom check",
  "135.title": "Not MD State",
  "135.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "135.problem": "Incorrect State Name - State name should be Maryland (are you in Maryland?)",
  "135.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "135.solution": "Verify correct state name on segment",
  "136.enabled": true,
  "136.params": {
    "titleEN": "Wrong name on Maryland Route",
    "problemEN": "All primary routes should be named MD-### in Maryland",
    "solutionEN": "Change name to MD-###",
    "template": "${state}:##${street}##${altStreet[0]}##${altStreet[1]}##${altStreet[2]}##${altStreet[3]}##${altStreet[4]}##${altStreet[5]}##${altStreet[6]}##${altStreet[7]}##${altStreet[8]}##${altStreet[9]}",
    "regexp": "/^Maryland:.*(?:State Hwy |State Rd |State Rte |MD |MD Hwy |MD-Hwy |M D |SH-)(?:[1-5]{0,1}[1-9]{0,2})( [SNEW])?#/i"
  },
  "136.solutionLink": "W:Maryland#Roads",
  "136.title.en": "Custom check",
  "136.title": "Wrong name on Maryland Route",
  "136.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "136.problem": "All primary routes should be named MD-### in Maryland",
  "136.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "136.solution": "Change name to MD-###",
  "139.enabled": true,
  "139.params": {
    "titleEN": "Bad Street Name",
    "problemEN": "Street Name has been identified as mass entered name that is incorrect. (dfa, nul, or null)",
    "solutionEN": "Correct the street name to remove dfa, nul, or null",
    "template": "${street}##${altStreet[0]}##${altStreet[1]}##${altStreet[2]}##${altStreet[3]}##${altStreet[4]}##${altStreet[5]}##${altStreet[6]}##${altStreet[7]}##${altStreet[8]}##${altStreet[9]}",
    "regexp": ".*\\b(dfa|nul|null)\\b/i"
  },
  "139.solutionLink": "W:Road_types/USA#Primary_Street",
  "139.title.en": "Custom check",
  "139.title": "Bad Street Name",
  "139.problem.en": "The segment matched custom conditions",
  "139.problem": "Street Name has been identified as mass entered name that is incorrect. (dfa, nul, or null)",
  "139.solution.en": "Solve the issue",
  "139.solution": "Correct the street name to remove dfa, nul, or null",
  "150.enabled": true,
  "150.title.en": "No lock on Freeway",
  "150.title": "No lock on Freeway",
  "150.problem.en": "The Freeway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "150.problem": "The Freeway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "150.solution.en": "Lock the segment",
  "150.solution": "Lock the segment",
  "151.enabled": true,
  "151.title.en": "No lock on Major Highway",
  "151.title": "No lock on Major Highway",
  "151.problem.en": "The Major Highway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "151.problem": "The Major Highway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "151.solution.en": "Lock the segment",
  "151.solution": "Lock the segment",
  "152.enabled": true,
  "152.title.en": "No lock on Minor Highway",
  "152.title": "No lock on Minor Highway",
  "152.problem.en": "The Minor Highway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "152.problem": "The Minor Highway segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "152.solution.en": "Lock the segment",
  "152.solution": "Lock the segment",
  "153.enabled": true,
  "153.title.en": "No lock on Ramp",
  "153.title": "No lock on Ramp",
  "153.problem.en": "The Ramp segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "153.problem": "The Ramp segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "153.solution.en": "Lock the segment",
  "153.solution": "Lock the segment",
  "154.enabled": true,
  "154.title.en": "No lock on Primary Street",
  "154.title": "No lock on Primary Street",
  "154.problem.en": "The Primary Street segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "154.problem": "The Primary Street segment should be locked at least to Lvl ${n}",
  "154.solution.en": "Lock the segment",
  "154.solution": "Lock the segment",
  "170.params": {
    "regexp": "/^(?!(to) [^a-z])((S|N|W|E) )?[a-z]/"
  },
  "171.enabled": true,
  "171.params": {
    "regexp": "/((?!(\\bPhila|\\bPenna|.(\\bWash|\\bCmdr|\\bProf|\\bPres)|..(\\bAdm|\\bSte|\\bCpl|\\bMaj|\\bSgt|\\bRe[vc]|\\bR\\.R|\\bGov|\\bGen|\\bHon|\\bCpl)|...(\\bSt|\\b[JSD]r|\\bLt|\\bFt)|...(#| )[NEWSR])).{5}\\.|((?!(hila|enna|(\\bWash|\\bCmdr|\\bProf|\\bPres)|.(\\bAdm|\\bSte|\\bCpl|\\bMaj|\\bSgt|\\bRe[vc]|\\bR\\.R|\\bGov|\\bGen|\\bHon|\\bCpl)|..(\\bSt|\\b[JSD]r|\\bLt|\\bFt)|..(#| )[NEWSR])).{4}|(\\bhila|\\benna))\\.|((?!(ila|nna|(ash|mdr|rof|res)|(\\bAdm|\\bSte|\\bCpl|\\bMaj|\\bSgt|\\bRe[vc]|\\bR\\.R|\\bGov|\\bGen|\\bHon|\\bCpl)|.(\\bSt|\\b[JSD]r|\\bLt|\\bFt)|.(#| )[NEWSR])).{3}|\\b(ila|nna|ash|mdr|rof|res))\\.|((?!(la|na|(sh|dr|of|es)|(dm|te|pl|aj|gt|e[vc]|\\.R|ov|en|on|pl)|(\\bSt|\\b[JSD]r|\\bLt|\\bFt)|(#| )[NEWSR])).{2}|\\b(la|na|sh|dr|of|es|dm|te|pl|aj|gt|e[vc]|\\.R|ov|en|on|pl))\\.|(#|^)[^NEWSR]?\\.)|(((?!\\b(D|O|L)).|#|^)'(?![sl]\\b)|(#|^)'s|(?!\\b(In|Na)t).{3}'l|(#|^).{0,2}'l)|(Dr|St)\\.(#|$)|,|;|\\\\|((?!\\.( |#|$|R))\\..|(?!\\.( .|#.|$|R\\.))\\..{2}|\\.R(#|$|\\.R))|[Ee]x(p|w)y\\b|Tunl\\b|Long Is\\b|Brg\\b/",
    "problemEN": "The street name has incorrect abbreviation, or character",
    "solutionEN": "Check upper/lower case, a space before/after the abbreviation and the accordance with the abbreviation table. Remove any comma (,), backslash (\\), or semicolon (;)"
  },
  "171.solutionLink": "W:Abbreviations_and_acronyms/USA#Standard_suffix_abbreviations",
  "171.title.en": "Incorrectly abbreviated street name",
  "171.title": "Incorrectly abbreviated street name",
  "171.problem.en": "The street name has incorrect abbreviation",
  "171.problem": "The street name has incorrect abbreviation",
  "171.solution.en": "Check upper/lower case, a space before/after the abbreviation and the accordance with the abbreviation table",
  "171.solution": "Check upper/lower case, a space before/after the abbreviation and the accordance with the abbreviation table",
  "172.title.en": "Unneeded spaces in street name",
  "172.title": "Unneeded spaces in street name",
  "172.problem.en": "Leading/trailing/double space in the street name",
  "172.problem": "Leading/trailing/double space in the street name",
  "172.solution.en": "Remove unneeded spaces from the street name",
  "172.solution": "Remove unneeded spaces from the street name",
  "173.title.en": "No space before/after street abbreviation",
  "173.title": "No space before/after street abbreviation",
  "173.problem.en": "No space before ('1943r.') or after ('st.Jan') an abbreviation in the street name",
  "173.problem": "No space before ('1943r.') or after ('st.Jan') an abbreviation in the street name",
  "173.solution.en": "Add a space before/after the abbreviation",
  "173.solution": "Add a space before/after the abbreviation",
  "175.title.en": "Empty street name",
  "175.title": "Empty street name",
  "175.problem.en": "The street name has only space characters or a dot",
  "175.problem": "The street name has only space characters or a dot",
  "175.solution.en": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name, click 'Apply' OR set a proper street name",
  "175.solution": "In the address properties check the 'None' box next to the street name, click 'Apply' OR set a proper street name",
  "190.title.en": "Lowercase city name",
  "190.title": "Lowercase city name",
  "190.problem.en": "The city name starts with a lowercase letter",
  "190.problem": "The city name starts with a lowercase letter",
  "190.solution.en": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "190.solution": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "192.title.en": "Unneeded spaces in city name",
  "192.title": "Unneeded spaces in city name",
  "192.problem.en": "Leading/trailing/double space in the city name",
  "192.problem": "Leading/trailing/double space in the city name",
  "192.solution.en": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "192.solution": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "193.title.en": "No space before/after city abbreviation",
  "193.title": "No space before/after city abbreviation",
  "193.problem.en": "No space before ('1943r.') or after ('st.Jan') an abbreviation in the city name",
  "193.problem": "No space before ('1943r.') or after ('st.Jan') an abbreviation in the city name",
  "193.solution.en": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "193.solution": "Use this form to rename the city",
  "200.title.en": "Node A: Unconfirmed turn on minor road",
  "200.title": "Node A: Unconfirmed turn on minor road",
  "200.problem.en": "The minor drivable segment has an unconfirmed (soft) turn at node A",
  "200.problem": "The minor drivable segment has an unconfirmed (soft) turn at node A",
  "200.solution.en": "Click the turn indicated with a purple question mark to confirm it. Note: you may need to make the segment 'Two-way' in order to see those turns",
  "200.solution": "Click the turn indicated with a purple question mark to confirm it. Note: you may need to make the segment 'Two-way' in order to see those turns",
  "201.title.en": "Node A: Unconfirmed turn on primary road",
  "201.title": "Node A: Unconfirmed turn on primary road",
  "201.problem.en": "The primary segment has an unconfirmed (soft) turn at node A",
  "201.problem": "The primary segment has an unconfirmed (soft) turn at node A",
  "201.solution.en": "Click the turn indicated with a purple question mark to confirm it. Note: you may need to make the segment 'Two-way' in order to see those turns",
  "201.solution": "Click the turn indicated with a purple question mark to confirm it. Note: you may need to make the segment 'Two-way' in order to see those turns"
};
